<jobs>
    <job>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[CLIENT SUCCESS MANAGER]]>
        </title>
        <company>Joveo</company>
        <city>Hyderabad</city>
        <state>Telangana</state>
        <country>India</country>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
            Joveo is driving the next-generation of recruitment tech solutions globally. As our Senior Client Success Manager, you'll be a vital member of the founding team for Joveo Europe, based in London. You'll be earning a competitive salary, and we encourage flexible and remote working.

            As our Senior Customer Success Manager, you'll be responsible for managing multiple customers and serve as their primary Joveo contact and advisor. You'll be empowered to succeed in your client focussed role while working collaboratively with the Global Head of CS and MD for Joveo UK on our regional Client Success strategy.

            With previous experience as a Client Success Manager you'll thrive in a fast-paced environment and be passionate about using creativity to collaboratively solve problems: helping our awesome customers win!]]>
        </description>
        <referencenumber>1</referencenumber>
        <url>https://www.joveo.com/careers</url>
        <date>2019-11-24</date>
        <category>Recruitment</category>
        <department>Recruitment</department>
    </job>
    <job>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[
            CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER
    ]]>
        </title>
        <company>Joveo</company>
        <city>Redwood City</city>
        <state>California</state>
        <country>United States</country>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[With brilliant people and innovative AI/ML technologies, Joveo is driving the next-generation of recruitment tech solutions globally. As a Customer Success Manager, you will be a key member of our fast-growing Customer Success Team. You will be responsible for managing multiple customers and serve as their primary Joveo interface, advisor and advocate. The ideal candidate thrives in a fast-paced environment and is passionate about being a customer advocate and a trusted strategic advisor by constantly acquiring and upgrading the required skills and domain knowledge. You build strong and long-lasting relationships with your customers and your efforts will drive customer satisfaction and happiness.]]>
        </description>
        <referencenumber>2</referencenumber>
        <url>https://www.joveo.com/careers</url>
        <date>2019-11-24</date>
        <category>Recruitment</category>
        <department>Recruitment</department>
    </job>
    <job>
        <title>
            <![CDATA[ Senior Software Engineer]]>
        </title>
        <company>Joveo</company>
        <city>Hyderabad</city>
        <state>Telangana</state>
        <country>India</country>s
        <description>
            <![CDATA[

    Joveo is an exciting programmatic media start-up with grand ambitions; ‘a job for everyone’. Harnessing machine learning and big data, our platform connects our clients with the right candidates for the right roles, faster and more efficiently than ever before. Through brilliant people and innovative technology, we are driving next generation recruitment technology solutions.
    We have a unique culture which embodies the core values of the company - transparency, teamwork, integrity and ownership.
     We believe in faster iterations, deploying code into production on a daily basis, heavy focus on customer delight, flat hierarchy, and fun environment.
    Responsibilities
    You will be part of a small team, with a large amount of ownership and responsibility for managing things directly.
    You will ship high quality solutions with a sense of urgency and speed.
    You will work closely with product managers, other teams, and both internal and external stakeholders, owning a large part of the process from problem understanding to shipping the solution.
    You will have the freedom to suggest and drive organization-wide initiatives.
    Requirements
    4+ Years of Experience as a Development Engineer with Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, computer engineering, electrical engineering or equivalent work experience
    Experience with at least one the following languages: Scala, Java, and/or any functional language. We code primarily in Scala, so you’ll be excited to either ramp up on that or continue building awesome things with it.
    Experience with software engineering best practices (e.g. unit testing, code reviews, design documentation).
    A blend of product, system, and people knowledge that lets you jump into a fast paced environment and contribute from day one
    An ability to balance a sense of urgency with shipping high quality and pragmatic solutions
    Extensive experience working with a large codebase and cross functional team
    Self-motivation and an enjoyment for a startup environment


    Benefits
    Talented and collaborative coworkers who will both push and support you
    Market competitive salary
    Stock options
    Flat Hirerachy
    26 weeks maternity leave so you can truly bond with your child
    Paid Leaves
    Work from home options
    Sick leaves are never counted at Joveo
    Every day lunch and snacks
    Team outings, parties and Unlimited fun


    ]]>
        </description>
        <referencenumber>3</referencenumber>
        <url>https://www.joveo.com/careers</url>
        <date>2019-11-26</date>
        <category>Engineering</category>
    </job>
</jobs>